<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Ascher & Denton - Family Law with Compassion & Integrity  360-357-8669 2401 Bristol Ct. SW #A-101, Olympia, WA ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Ascher & Denton - Family Law with Compassion & Integrity  360-357-8669 2401 Bristol Ct. SW #A-101, Olympia, WA ]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:52:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olympia, Washington Family Law & Divorce Lawyers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1></h1><p>This focus is not about being cheap, it is about providing the best value and doing things right with long term consequences in mind. Litigation is exhausting and expensive and we avoid wasted time and avoid hurting anyone's feelings as much as possible. It is just the right way to do family law.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e7a5e1ab-b8e3-424b-970e-4c51c33ec28d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/olympia-washington-family-law-and-divorce-lawyers/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">58e5cd13-f8f2-4499-9b5e-7516a511c056</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:20:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Lawyers Who Help Families Minimize Pain & Expense  Since 1990, achieving best family outcomes with minimal conflict and expense Located in Olympia, Washington, we provide compassionate and considered advice and representation in all areas of family law, with the philosophy that respect and sensible negotiation often provide the best results: Divorce/Dissolution of Marriage Alimony/Spousal Support Child custody and visitation/Parenting Plans Child support (past/present/future) Domestic Violence Protection Orders Child support modification and enforcement Unmarried couple property division Mediation/ Collaborative Law/ One Lawyer Non Parental Custody Adoption Divorce We focus on helping you figure out what your best options are and cut your losses when making decisions about your divorce, including fair distribution of assets, division of the marital home, child support payments and child custody rights. (In Washington, Divorce is called Dissolution of Marriage and Child Custody is called Parenting Plan)  Alimony Reasonable spousal support is sometimes appropriate in a divorce. Attorney fees awards are sometimes involved to help a less financially able spouse have a lawyer. We work within the boundaries of the law to help get spousal support established in a reasonable amount and for a reasonable length of time so both parties can go on with their lives with dignity.   Child custody and visitation Washington law protects the constitutional rights of both parents to parent while the primary basis for all decisions about parenting plans is always "the best interest of the child" standard. Our law firm tries hard to work with our client and the court (and the other side, when possible) to reach toward the very best parenting plan solutions for both parents to have appropriate and meaningful contact with their children.  Child support Washington State Laws provide for a standard set of guidelines for parents to provide support for their children. It is an art, not an automatic result, to work within these guidelines to insure that children are supported in the correct way as intended by the law. We focus on obeying the law and getting to a reasonable result that both parents can live with to support their children. It is important to do an intelligent cost benefit analysis in every case and for you to make informed decisions for past/present and future support and interest that may be owed.  Child support modification and enforcement Child support payments do not change unless the court or administrative process modifies the child support order. If either the custodial or the noncustodial parent experiences a significant change in circumstances, our attorneys can guide you through the proper legal procedures to modify your child support payments accordingly.   Mediation  Mediation puts the decisions in your hands and can often provide more expedient, predictable results than a trial.  Much of the time, we resolve family law cases outside of court. The skilled negotiators at Ascher & Denton, PLLC can help you obtain the most equitable divorce settlement.   Contact us for an initial consultation  Call Ascher & Denton, PLLC at 360-357-8669 or contact us online to schedule an appointment with a family law attorney for cases in Thurston County, Mason County or Lewis County, Washington.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/lawyers-who-help-families-minimize-pain-and-expense-since-199/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">80f6f6c3-462f-4531-a128-00649e911084</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>This Olympia Divorce Law Firm Advocates for Best Family Outcomes Olympia lawyers seek dispute resolution with minimal expense and discord The dissolution of your marriage is an emotional and stressful event. The compassionate attorneys at Ascher & Denton, PLLC help ease the legal strain of divorce so you can concentrate on the health and well-being of your family.   With more than 20 years of experience in family law matters, the attorneys at Ascher & Denton, PLLC in Olympia take your individual needs into account as we seek the best possible results for you regarding: Child custody and visitation rights Child support Distribution of personal property, bank accounts, stocks and other assets Division of marital debts Sale or possession of the marital home Spousal support and temporary support  Family law mediators who encourage cooperation Mediation gives you and your spouse the opportunity to negotiate a divorce settlement in a more amicable setting by working with a trained facilitator. The mediation process fosters cooperation between partners and produces less stress and hostility than is usually associated with litigation. Mediation often reduces the time and costs of divorce, and it puts the decisions in your hands. The experienced negotiators at Ascher & Denton, PLLC can help you obtain the most equitable divorce settlement, fair child support agreement and healthy child custody arrangement.   Family law litigators by your side At Ascher & Denton, PLLC, our attorneys work hard to resolve divorce issues outside of court. We are courteous and respectful to all parties throughout the process and encourage our clients to take this approach, too. However, sometimes litigation is necessary to resolve your family’s disputes. Having a strong litigator by your side can alleviate the uncertainty and stress of the arduous litigation process and help you obtain the most favorable trial outcome. Lawyers at Ascher & Denton, LLC use smart trial strategies to get the best result for you and your family throughout the litigation process.   Contact a family law attorney for a consultation Call Ascher & Denton, PLLC at 360-357-8669 or contact us online for an initial consultation on your divorce case. We are committed to delivering the best outcome for you and your family with minimal conflict and expense.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/this-olympia-divorce-law-firm-advocates-for-best-family-outc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9a2ea2dc-6bb3-4331-822a-8489404881a5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Are Family Law Attorneys in Washington  Who Resolve Child Custody Conflicts]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We Are Family Law Attorneys in Washington  Who Resolve Child Custody Conflicts</h1><p> Compassionate lawyers with more than 25 years of experience negotiating  best outcomes for families. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7f9a2dca6c88159c36c48c35c799add3484d0ff1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/child-custody.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b909fdbe-abc9-4933-a507-ed1b6b3cc511</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ONE LAWYER]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ONE LAWYER</h1><p>The lawyer makes sure filing deadlines are known and rights preserved. Any lawyer who provide One Lawyer services have ten or more years of subject area practice experience and excellent credentials. Less experienced lawyers can act as One Lawyer if they consult with such an experienced lawyer as a mentor to review each significant legal issue. The highest standards of legal practice must be used and the lawyer has an ethical duty not to allow parties to abuse an imbalance of power or to reach illegal or unethical agreements.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/63973c384c13f41b4c51e4ecbb5df4746200930b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/one-lawyer-services.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0190fb4b-c2ef-45b9-ae3a-13ee3ff92e82</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 23:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[At Ascher & Denton, we only practice Family Law. ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>At Ascher & Denton, we only practice Family Law. </h1><p>If you think that we are simple folk who only do the same thing over and over, think again. Each family is different from all others and different at each moment in the process of change while going through the trauma of a family law case. Family law also most always includes vital decisions on most other areas of law - especially bankruptcy, tax, employment, housing, criminal, and business law. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/278e3bc4921700de940937f295a3dc3b3736357b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/melissa-denton.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6e507e4c-9ed2-4ce9-91cc-16afce23ef0d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:08:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Khrys Kayne, Legal Assistant ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Khrys Kayne, Legal Assistant </h1><p> Khrys came to work at Ascher & Denton in late 2013 as an intern when she was nearing completion of her associate's degree at Spokane Community College. She proved herself so invaluable that she came to work here permanently in January of 2014 and has stayed with us since.   Khrys is now enrolled at The Evergreen State College (Kaylene's and Jim's alma mater) where she will complete her bachelor's degree in January 2017. Khrys has two wonderful daughters and two cats. She celebrated eleven years clean from drug use on January 1, 2015. Khrys is contemplating what her next career goals will be. She may decide to become an attorney and many of our clients would approve heartily.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3f343fba39b011f068193027bf4f39e30dbf929b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/khrys-kayne.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e8157a02-eca2-4e68-879f-60b4ac7fea6b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kaylene Petitt, Law Clerk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Kaylene Petitt, Law Clerk</h1><p> In Janurary of 2008, Kaylene started as a legal assistant with Ascher & Denton. Armed with her bachelor's degree from The Evergreen State College, emphasizing United States History and Visual Arts and great life skills, Kaylene has blossomed in her law office careers.  Through many life changes and through many many residence moves, Kaylene has been a crucial part of the Ascher & Denton team.   Kaylene's compassionate and careful, clear approach to helping clients and helping to run the business side of this firm make her a wonderful asset and a really enjoyable person to get help from. In mid 2015, Kaylene started her four year course of study as a Law Clerk (with Melissa Denton's mentoring) to become an attorney with this firm. She also enjoys cooking and sharing delicious food, taking pictures of her cat, and being a newlywed.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3fddd9e3d278e9f634aeedbbb7428b9afc7629b4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/kaylene-petitt.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">607a6c2a-b3c7-4bd4-8d55-a500c176b3c8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Melissa Denton, Family Law Attorney ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Melissa Denton, Family Law Attorney </h1><p>Melissa Denton is the founding partner and senior lawyer at Ascher & Denton. She has practiced family law in Thurston County since 1990.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ab92cd9df9d8a9e921ccb7b558a3b89e24dada17.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/melissa-denton.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02340a65-61f7-42b2-9412-92fab42068cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:15:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bdc8b7bb-912b-4e94-ad57-9e3d39009a9b.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/our-philosophy.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88a3b5ef-f61e-4df9-94ec-85954bae7820</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 21:56:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>