<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Olympia, Washington Family Lawyer Ascher & Denton]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Olympia, Washington Family Lawyer Ascher & Denton]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:31:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olympia, Washington Family Law & Divorce Lawyers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1></h1><p>Family law with compassion and integrity, since 1990</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/olympia-washington-family-law-and-divorce-lawyers/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">58e5cd13-f8f2-4499-9b5e-7516a511c056</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:31:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.ascherdenton.com/uploads/1/9/1/5/19151845/6746988.jpg?250">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/8d37935f-456b-4f40-8a19-79e334fa0f5b/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8d37935f-456b-4f40-8a19-79e334fa0f5b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:28:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Melissa Denton, senior partner attorney    Melissa practices only in the area of Family Law - including many things like: Divorce; Child Custody; Child Support; Collaborative Law; Settlement Law; Alimony; Annulment; Cohabitation Agreements; Collaborative Family Law; Community Property Law; Divorce Arbitration; Divorce Mediation; Divorce Taxation; Domestic Partnerships; Domestic Relations; Domestic Violence; Equitable Distribution; Family Arbitration; Family Mediation; Gay and Lesbian Family Law; International Family Law; Interstate Support; Marital Agreements; Marital Property Distribution; Marital Property Law; Marital Property Settlements; Matrimonial Law; Military Divorce; Non-Traditional Family Law; Paternity; Post Divorce Modification; Postnuptial Agreements; Premarital Agreements; Qualified Domestic Relations Orders (QDROs); Restraining Orders; Separation Agreements; Spousal Support; Uncontested Divorce   Admitted to the Washington State Bar in 1989, as well as to practice before the US Federal District Court for Western Washington  Law Schools: Juris Doctorate Degree from The University of Oklahoma School of Law in 1985, including studies at The Queen's College, University of Oxford in England Undergraduate Schools: Bachelor of Arts Degree and some graduate school: University of Oklahoma in Norman, Oklahoma, with a major in history and a minor in psychology, along with studies in electrical engineering and physical therapy and a summer studying Political Science and History at Rewley House, University of Oxford summer program on scholarship.  Bar Affiliations: Thurston County (Member, Family Law Section; Former President and Founding Member of Thurston County Young Lawyers) and Washington State (Former Member, Board of Trustees, Young Lawyers Division) Bar Associations.  Melissa's focus is on helping folks who want to resolve their cases with a minimum of ugly court action. While the courts are useful when folks just can't agree, it is so much wiser to handle personal family issues privately and with a minimum of expense when reasonable agreements can be reached. When the court is needed, Melissa tries to keep that expensive alternative to a minimum so that families can begin to heal in a new form rather than being further damaged by the adversarial process required in court.   Melissa has pioneered a new way of practicing law, called One Lawyer, and also began a business called AdvantageDenton.com which finds the right lawyer for clients.   Melissa represented a client from the beginning of a divorce though two appellate court cases and up through the Supreme Court of Washington in a very important case called In re Marriage of Rideout,. 150 Wn.2d 337, 359, 77 P.3d 1174 (2003)  Melissa has been married since 1987 and has a teenage son who plans to be a lawyer, heaven help us all. Melissa's family is in Oklahoma and her husband's family is in Malaysia, so they travel a lot. Melissa got her black belt in Shorin Ryu Karate right before starting law school. It helped.  .</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/melissa-denton-senior-partner-attorney-melissa-practices/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02340a65-61f7-42b2-9412-92fab42068cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:28:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our Philosophy (The way we work)  Ascher & Denton, PLLC was created with some very clear goals in mind. We feel it is vitally important to assist our clients through controversies involving the legal system at the least cost to the client, financially and emotionally. Treating each other and others with respect is paramount. Compassion is important, as is clear thinking and honesty. We believe that inflicting unneeded costs (or pain) on others is a big mistake. A law of physics also applies to lawsuits: every action brings an equal and opposite reaction.   We believe it is smart to be professionally courteous to opposing counsel and to opposing parties. We work hard to maintain our excellent reputation in the legal community. Much of the time, the court does not make the decision for our client, because we work out a reasonable solution in an agreement with the other side. When you have anyone else, even a knowledgeable judicial officer, make your decisions for you, everyone risks being unhappy with the result.   When it is possible to reach a result that is satisfactory to our client, we avoid wasting time and money on unnecessary court hearings or unneeded formal discovery. We work as a team with the client. We focus on helping people. When you do what is right the best you can, you do not need to spend client money on protecting the lawyer instead of serving the client.   Although we are not completely perfect at all times, we certainly strive towards that goal. We believe we should be worthy of the trust of opposing parties and their attorneys, as well as the trust of our clients. This helps us to achieve good results for our clients. We believe that being trustworthy helps us best fulfill our role as officers of the courts and agents of the judicial system.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/our-philosophy-the-way-we-work-ascher-and-denton-pllc-was/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88a3b5ef-f61e-4df9-94ec-85954bae7820</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:28:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olympia, Washington, Family Law | Ascher & Denton]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Olympia, Washington, Family Law | Ascher & Denton</h1><p>Family law attorneys in Olympia, Washington. Compassionate and efficient help through divorce and child custody problems.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ascherdenton.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e1f02ac7-6f9f-4308-aa65-d5e3172965d3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Melissa Denton, senior partner attorney]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Melissa Denton, senior partner attorney</h1><h2>Melissa Denton, senior partner attorney</h2><p>null</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ascherdenton/melissa-denton-senior-partner-attorney/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">066534af-668b-47a6-bbda-067597001e37</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>